export const baumlisteData =
{
  '0-10 Baumliste': {
    title: '0-10 Baumliste',
    questions: [
      { question: '0.', answer: 'Tropfen (Regen)' },
      { question: '1.', answer: 'Baum' },
      { question: '2.', answer: 'Lichtschalter' },
      { question: '3.', answer: 'Hocker' },
      { question: '4.', answer: 'Auto' },
      { question: '5.', answer: 'Hand' },
      { question: '6.', answer: 'Würfel' },
      { question: '7.', answer: 'Zwerg' },
      { question: '8.', answer: 'Achterbahn' },
      { question: '9.', answer: 'Katze' },
      { question: '10.', answer: 'Bibel' },
    ]},

  '11-20 Baumliste': {
    title: '11-20 Baumliste',
    questions: [
      { question: '11.', answer: 'Fußball(mannschaft)' },
      { question: '12.', answer: 'Geist' },
      { question: '13.', answer: 'Fahrstuhl' },
      { question: '14.', answer: 'Herz' },
      { question: '15.', answer: 'Ritter' },
      { question: '16.', answer: 'Teenager' },
      { question: '17.', answer: 'Kartenspiel' },
      { question: '18.', answer: 'Abendverkehr' },
      { question: '19.', answer: 'Abendessen' },
      { question: '20.', answer: 'Tagesschau' },
    ]},

  '21-30 Schlafzimmer': {
    title: '21-30 Schlafzimmer',
    questions: [
      { question: '21.', answer: 'Bett' },
      { question: '22.', answer: 'Kissen' },
      { question: '23.', answer: 'Bettdecke' },
      { question: '24.', answer: 'Nachttisch' },
      { question: '25.', answer: 'Wecker' },
      { question: '26.', answer: 'Schublade' },
      { question: '27.', answer: 'Vorhänge' },
      { question: '28.', answer: 'Mond' },
      { question: '29.', answer: 'Sterne' },
      { question: '30.', answer: 'Kleiderschrank' },
    ]},

  '31-40 Badezimmer': {
    title: '31-40 Badezimmer',
    questions: [
      { question: '31.', answer: 'Badewanne' },
      { question: '32.', answer: 'Duschvorhang' },
      { question: '33.', answer: 'Schwamm' },
      { question: '34.', answer: 'Seife' },
      { question: '35.', answer: 'Badetücher' },
      { question: '36.', answer: 'Spiegelschrank' },
      { question: '37.', answer: 'Waschbecken' },
      { question: '38.', answer: 'Zahnbürste' },
      { question: '39.', answer: 'Rasierapparat' },
      { question: '40.', answer: 'Toilette' },
    ]},

  '41-50 Küche': {
    title: '41-50 Küche',
    questions: [
      { question: '41', answer: 'Herd' },
      { question: '42', answer: 'Pfanne' },
      { question: '43', answer: 'Spüle (Spülbecken)' },
      { question: '44', answer: 'Abfalleimer' },
      { question: '45', answer: 'Kühlschrank' },
      { question: '46', answer: 'Milch' },
      { question: '47', answer: 'Butter' },
      { question: '48', answer: 'Mikrowelle' },
      { question: '49', answer: 'Teller' },
      { question: '50', answer: 'Besteck' },
    ]},

  '51-60 Wohnzimmer': {
    title: '51-60 Wohnzimmer',
    questions: [
      { question: '51', answer: 'Sofa' },
      { question: '52', answer: 'Tisch' },
      { question: '53', answer: 'Lampe' },
      { question: '54', answer: 'Schrank (Bücherschrank - regal)' },
      { question: '55', answer: 'Fernseher' },
      { question: '56', answer: 'Stereoanlage' },
      { question: '57', answer: 'Videorekorder' },
      { question: '58', answer: 'Fernbedienung' },
      { question: '59', answer: 'Blumen Pflanze' },
      { question: '60', answer: 'Teppich' },
    ]},

  '61-70 Garten': {
    title: '61-70 Garten',
    questions: [
      { question: '61', answer: 'Weg' },
      { question: '62', answer: 'Zaun' },
      { question: '63', answer: 'Sandkasten' },
      { question: '64', answer: 'Schaufel' },
      { question: '65', answer: 'Rasenmäher' },
      { question: '66', answer: 'Rasen' },
      { question: '67', answer: 'Wasserschlauch' },
      { question: '68', answer: 'Gartenmöbel' },
      { question: '69', answer: 'Schaukel' },
      { question: '70', answer: 'Brunnen' },
    ]},

  '71-80 Büro': {
    title: '71-80 Büro',
    questions: [
      { question: '71', answer: 'Schreibtisch' },
      { question: '72', answer: 'Papier' },
      { question: '73', answer: 'Schreibzeug' },
      { question: '74', answer: '(Telefon) / Tafel' },
      { question: '75', answer: 'Computer' },
      { question: '76', answer: 'Tastatur' },
      { question: '77', answer: 'Drucker' },
      { question: '78', answer: 'Kabel' },
      { question: '79', answer: '(Schrank)- Ordner' },
      { question: '80', answer: '(Faxgerät) / Papierkorb' },
    ]},

  '81-90 Auto': {
    title: '81-90 Auto',
    questions: [
      { question: '81', answer: 'Stoßstange' },
      { question: '82', answer: 'Motorhaube' },
      { question: '83', answer: 'Scheibenwischer' },
      { question: '84', answer: 'Scheibe' },
      { question: '85', answer: 'Lenkrad' },
      { question: '86', answer: 'Hupe' },
      { question: '87', answer: 'Gangschaltung' },
      { question: '88', answer: 'Radio' },
      { question: '89', answer: 'Handschuhfach' },
      { question: '90', answer: 'Kofferraum' },
    ]},

  '91-100 Körperliste': {
    title: '91-100 Körperliste',
    questions: [
      { question: '91', answer: 'Fuß / Schuh' },
      { question: '92', answer: 'Knie' },
      { question: '93', answer: 'Oberschenkel' },
      { question: '94', answer: 'Po' },
      { question: '95', answer: 'Taille' },
      { question: '96', answer: 'Brust' },
      { question: '97', answer: 'Schultern' },
      { question: '98', answer: 'Hals' },
      { question: '99', answer: 'Gesicht' },
      { question: '100', answer: 'Haare' }
    ]}, }
